<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfTitleDescriptionArray xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>WWE Championship</titlename>
    <description>The WWE Championship is widely recognized as the most historic championship in WWE. Dating back to 1963, the WWE Championship was first awarded to Buddy Rogers after he defeated Antonino Rocca in the finals of a tournament in April. Since that time, the biggest names in the business have held the WWE Championship, including Bruno Sammartino, Andre the Giant, Bret Hart, The Rock, Stone Cold and many more.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>World Heavyweight Championship</titlename>
    <description>The World Heavyweight Championship was brought to Raw by then-General Manager Eric Bischoff after WWE Champion Brock Lesnar became exclusive to SmackDown. Bischoff awarded the championship to Triple H, but he had to defend it against his then-best friend, Ric Flair. Triple H was successful and has held the championship on five different occasions. Other holders of this prestigious championship include Shawn Michaels, Undertaker, Rey Mysterio and more.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>United States Championship</titlename>
    <description>Unlike most other championships currently defended on Raw and SmackDown, the United States Championship did not start out as a recognized WWE Championship. Rather, the U.S. Championship got its roots in WCW. Many of the ring's greatest names have staked claim to the U.S. Title during the title's early years, including WWE Hall of Famers Sgt. Slaughter and Greg Valentine. With each great name that captured the championship came more prestige. In the late 1990s, however, the U.S. Championship was vacated more times than WWE fans could keep up with. As a result, the championship lost a bit of its luster. Years later, the U.S. Championship finally regained the glory it held in years past when competitors like Eddie Guerrero, Booker T and John Cena fought over it in many memorable battles.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>Intercontinental Championship</titlename>
    <description>The Intercontinental Championship has been viewed as one of the most prestigious awards in the world of wrestling. Since its inception in September 1979, many greats have captured the Intercontinental Championship, including Hall of Famers Pat Patterson, Don Muraco, Tito Santana and Greg Valentine. Additionally, many of today's top Superstars have enjoyed reigns as Intercontinental Champion, including Shawn Michaels, The Rock, Chris Jericho and Triple H. Below is the complete list of Intercontinental Champions. Click on each name for more information on the champion.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>WWE Tag Team Championship</titlename>
    <description>While the WWE Tag Team Championship only dates back to 2002, it is still considered one of the most prestigious championships in the history of tag team wrestling. The championship got its start after it was decided that the World Tag Team Championship would be exclusive to the Raw brand. After this announcement, then-SmackDown General Manager Stephanie McMahon created her own version of the World Tag Team Championship. She then declared that the first champions would be the duo that survived a brutal tournament. Since that time, many great tag teams have staked claim to the prestigious championship, including John Morrison &amp; The Miz and Los Guerreros. The WWE Tag Team Championship was previously known as the Unified Tag Team Championship when it was combined with the World Tag Team Championship at the 25th Anniversary of WrestleMania.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
  <TitleDescriptionArray>
    <titlename>WWE Tag Team Championship</titlename>
    <description>While the WWE Tag Team Championship only dates back to 2002, it is still considered one of the most prestigious championships in the history of tag team wrestling. The championship got its start after it was decided that the World Tag Team Championship would be exclusive to the Raw brand. After this announcement, then-SmackDown General Manager Stephanie McMahon created her own version of the World Tag Team Championship. She then declared that the first champions would be the duo that survived a brutal tournament. Since that time, many great tag teams have staked claim to the prestigious championship, including John Morrison &amp; The Miz and Los Guerreros. The WWE Tag Team Championship was previously known as the Unified Tag Team Championship when it was combined with the World Tag Team Championship at the 25th Anniversary of WrestleMania.</description>
  </TitleDescriptionArray>
</ArrayOfTitleDescriptionArray>